Register of the Raymond Moley papers, 1902-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
- GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE, 1912-1969 (Boxes 2-62)
  - Donovan, Robert J., 1953 (Folder 62)
  - Donovan, William J., 1939-1941 (Folder 63)
  - Dooley, Edward, 1954 (Folder 64)
  - Doolittle, Albert S., 1952 (Folder 65)
  - Doorly, H., 1951 (Folder 66)
  - Dorfman, Boris W., 1934 (Folder 67)
  - Dorr, G. H., 1932 (Folder 68)
  - Dorsey, Thomas B., 1965 (Folder 69)
  - Doughberry, Donald C., 1938 (Folder 70)
  - Doughty, Isabel, 1928 (Folder 71)
  - Douglas, B. R., 1933 (Folder 72)
  - Douglas, Lewis W., 1934-1953 (Folder 73)
  - Douglas, Paul F., 1954 (Folder 74)
  - Douglas, Paul H., 1928-1956 (Folder 75)
  - Douglas, W. A. S., 1936 (Folder 76)
  - Douglas, William O., 1928-1939 (Folder 77)
  - Dowling, Eddie, 1949 (Folder 78)
  - Downey, Sheridan, 1940 (Folder 79)
  - Doyle, Ann, 1929 (Folder 80)
  - Doyle, Bertrim W., 1928 (Folder 81)
  - Doyle, Nicholas A., 1934 (Folder 82)
  - Dragonette, Fred, 1951 (Folder 83)
  - Draper, Arthur S., 1934 (Folder 84)
  - Dresser, Robert B., 1951 (Folder 85)
  - Dresser, Theodore, 1934 (Folder 86)
  - Drewry, John E., 1932-1957 (Folder 87)
  - Drinko, John D., 1965 (Folder 88)
  - Driscoll, Alfred E., 1951 (Folder 89)
  - Driscoll, Charles B., 1933-1939 (Folder 90)
  - Driver, L. Robert, 1951 (Folder 91)
  - Drossos, John A., 1934 (Folder 92)
  - Drown, Frank S., 1928 (Folder 93)
  - Drucker, Abraham, 1928 (Folder 94)
  - Drum, John, 1932 (Folder 95)
  - Drummond, J. Roscoe, 1935 (Folder 96)
  - Dubber, Margaret D., 1928 (Folder 97)
  - Dubinsky, David, 1943 (Folder 98)
  - Dublin, Louis I., 1929-1936 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - DuBrul, Steven M., 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Duckworth, Allen, 1952-1958 (Folder 3)
  - Dudley, Lionel E., 1936 (Folder 4)
  - Dudley, L. L., 1934-1935 (Folder 5)
  - Duell, Sloan and Pearce, Inc., 1961-1966 (Folder 6)
  - Duffus, R. L., 1934 (Folder 7)
  - Duffy, Julia M., 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Duggan, Stephen P., 1932-1936 (Folder 9)
  - Duhig, Charles W., 1944 (Folder 10)
  - Duke, F. D., 1937 (Folder 11)
  - Dulles, Allen W., 1961 (Folder 12)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1943-1951 (Folder 13)
  - Dunbar, J. R., 1934 (Folder 14)
  - Dunham, Lawrence B., 1927-1931 (Folder 15)
  - Dunmore, Walter T., 1919 (Folder 16)
  - Dunn, E. G., 1932 (Folder 17)
  - Dunn, Gano, 1936-1950 (Folder 18)
  - Dunn, Harris A., 1953 (Folder 19)
  - Dunn, Rogers C., 1941-1943 (Folder 20)
  - Dunn, Roy, 1951 (Folder 21)
  - Dunn, Stephen F., 1963 (Folder 22)
  - Dunn, W. E., 1939 (Folder 23)
  - Dupee, Mary C., 1931 (Folder 24)
  - DuPont, 1942 (Folder 25)
  - Durand, Margaret, 1936 (Folder 26)
  - Durant, W. C., 1936 (Folder 27)
  - Durbin, C. M., 1932 (Folder 28)
  - Durham, Frank S., 1934 (Folder 29)
  - Durning, Harry M., 1936 (Folder 30)
  - Durstine, Roy S., 1939 (Folder 31)
  - Duryea, Charles E., 1932 (Folder 32)
  - Dutton, Henry R., 1959 (Folder 33)
  - Dwan, Ralph H., 1931 (Folder 34)
  - Dwyer, Earle D., 1933 (Folder 35)
  - Dwyer, F. P., 1917 (Folder 36)
  - Dwyer, Thomas R., 1934 (Folder 37)
  - Dyer, Czar J., 1932 (Folder 38)
  - Dykstra, C. A., 1922-1950 (Folder 39)
  - Dykstra, Lillian G., 1943 (Folder 40)
  - Eady, Ross, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Eagle, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1939 (Folder 2)
  - Eagon, Kenneth Laflin, 1933 (Folder 3)
  - Earle, Edward Mead, 1933-1938 (Folder 4)
  - Early, Harry J., 1935 (Folder 5)
  - Early, Stephen T., 1934-1946 (Folder 6)
  - Easley, Ralph M., 1925-1934 (Folder 7)
  - Eason, M. W., 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Eastman, Jennie Balfour, 1932 (Folder 9)
  - Eastman, Max, 1940-1955 (Folder 10)
  - Eaton, Cyrus S., 1934-1951 (Folder 11)
  - Eaton, Thomas M., 1939 (Folder 12)
  - Eberstadt, F., 1934-1945 (Folder 13)
  - Eby, Hyatt, 1951 (Folder 14)
  - Eccles, David, 1951 (Folder 15)
  - Eckert, Robert E., 1917 (Folder 16)
  - Ede, William W., 1933-1934 (Folder 17)
  - Edens, J. Drake, Jr., 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Eder, George S., 1932 (Folder 19)
  - Edgar, John, n.d. (Folder 20)
  - Edwards, Daniel, 1932 (Folder 21)
  - Edwards, George P., 1937 (Folder 22)
  - Edwards, H. Lynn, 1963 (Folder 23)
  - Edwards, J. P., 1932 (Folder 24)
  - Edwards, J. R., 1932 (Folder 25)
  - Ehrlich, Max, 1934 (Folder 26)
  - Ehrmann, Herbert B., 1931 (Folder 27)
  - Eichel, Leslie, 1932 (Folder 28)
  - Eichel, Mabel Jacques, 1937 (Folder 29)
  - Eichler, Rudolph, 1956 (Folder 30)
  - Einfeld, S. Charles, 1932 (Folder 31)
  - Einhom, David, 1930 (Folder 32)
  - Einsele, Helga, 1938 (Folder 33)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1949-1962 (Folder 34)
  - Eisenhower, Edgar N., 1937-1943 (Folder 35)
  - Eisler, George, 1919 (Folder 36)
  - Ekdahl, Edward G., 1934 (Folder 37)
  - Ekern, Herman L., 1934 (Folder 38)
  - Elder, Charles S., 1938 (Folder 39)
  - Ellender, Allen J., 1963 (Folder 40)
  - Ellerbe, Paul, 1934 (Folder 41)
  - Elliott, Howard, 1954 (Folder 42)
  - Elliott, Forrest, 1934 (Folder 43)
  - Elliott, Osborn, 1958-1964 (Folder 44)
  - Elliott, William Y., 1932-1960 (Folder 45)
  - Ellis, A. H., 1934 (Folder 46)
  - Ellis, Clyde T., 1957-1961 (Folder 47)
  - Ellis, Ellen Deborah, 1932 (Folder 48)
  - Ellsworth, Fred W., 1930 (Folder 49)
  - Elmer, Fred E., 1919 (Folder 50)
  - Elmer, W. M., 1963 (Folder 51)
  - Elwell, C. E., 1961 (Folder 52)
  - Ely, Gertrude, 1928 (Folder 53)
  - Emerson, Guy, 1934-1936 (Folder 54)
  - Emmet, Grenville T., 1932 (Folder 55)
  - Emory University, 1933 (Folder 56)
  - Engel, Irving M., 1937 (Folder 57)
  - English, Earl, 1951 (Folder 58)
  - Epstein, Abraham, 1932-1939 (Folder 59)
  - Epstein, A. S., 1952 (Folder 60)
  - Epstein, Joseph H., 1947-1959 (Folder 61)
  - Esch, Leona Marie, 1927-1934 (Folder 62)
  - Eshleman, C. L., 1942 (Folder 63)
  - Esmond, Burton D., 1926 (Folder 64)
  - Espy, Willard R., 1956-1957 (Folder 65)
  - Esguerre, Edmond, 1931 (Folder 66)
  - Essary, J. F., 1933 (Folder 67)
  - Eudy, Harrison, 1924 (Folder 68)
  - Eusey, Charles, 1965 (Folder 69)
  - Eustis, Grace, 1944 (Folder 70)
  - Evans, Albert, Jr., 1951 (Folder 71)
  - Evans, David J., 1956-1958 (Folder 72)
  - Evans, John M., 1953 (Folder 73)
  - Evans, Joseph L., 1958 (Folder 74)
  - Evans, Luther H., 1939 (Folder 75)
  - Evans, M. Stanton, 1961-1965 (Folder 76)
  - Evans, William H., 1934 (Folder 77)
  - Evening World, New York, 1926 (Folder 78)
  - Everett, John V., 1939 (Folder 79)
  - Ewing, William H., 1962 (Folder 80)
  - Ewing, William L., 1932 (Folder 81)
  - Ezekiel, Mordecai, 1936 (Folder 82)
  - Fabrigant, Grace, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Fact, 1964 (Folder 2)
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1932 (Folder 3)
  - Fagan, Bernard, 1930 (Folder 4)
  - Fagenson, Gertrude, 1927-1928 (Folder 5)
  - Fahey, John H., 1932-1936 (Folder 6)
  - Fairbank, Robert, 1953 (Folder 7)
  - Fairchild, A. H. R., 1951 (Folder 8)
  - Fairchild, F. A., 1933 (Folder 9)
  - Fairchild, Milton, 1933 (Folder 10)
  - Fairfax, H. G., 1933 (Folder 11)
  - Fairlie, John A., 1928 (Folder 12)
  - Falk Foundation, 1953-1954 (Folder 13)
  - Fall, Albert B., 1941 (Folder 14)
  - Fannin, Paul, 1960 (Folder 15)
  - Farber, W. O., 1953 (Folder 16)
  - Faris, Barry, 1938 (Folder 17)
  - Farkas, Emil, 1933 (Folder 18)
  - Farlander, W. E., 1934 (Folder 19)
  - Farley, Edward P., 1934 (Folder 20)
  - Farley, James A., 1932-1965 (Folder 21)
  - Farley, Miriam S., 1934 (Folder 22)
  - Farmer, Garland R., 1934 (Folder 23)
  - Farmer, Zack J., 1934 (Folder 24)
  - Farra, Kathryn, 1932 (Folder 25)
  - Farrington, Charles, Jr., 1960 (Folder 26)
  - Farrington, Selwyn K., 1932 (Folder 27)
  - Faulkner, Alex H., 1955 (Folder 28)
  - Favy, R. B., 1934 (Folder 29)
  - Fay, Herbert R., 1934 (Folder 30)
  - Fay, Horace B., Jr., n.d. (Folder 31)
  - Fearing, J. L., 1932 (Folder 32)
  - Feather, William, 1920-1962 (Folder 33)
  - Feeney, Leonard, 1939 (Folder 34)
  - Fein, Abraham, 1934 (Folder 35)
  - Feis, Herbert, 1934-1939 (Folder 36)
  - Feldman, Israel R., 1931 (Folder 37)
  - Felix, David, 1964 (Folder 38)
  - Fell, J. Howard, 1932 (Folder 39)
  - Feller, Alexander, 1934 (Folder 40)
  - Fenderbosch, N. A., 1933 (Folder 41)
  - Ferenz, F. K., 1934 (Folder 42)
  - Ferguson, C. B., 1926 (Folder 43)
  - Ferguson, E. M., 1934 (Folder 44)
  - Ferguson, Homer, 1953-1954 (Folder 45)
  - Ferris, W. M., 1934 (Folder 46)
  - Fertig, Maldwin, 1933 (Folder 47)
  - Fesler, Mayo, 1923 (Folder 48)
  - Feuge, T. W., 1934 (Folder 49)
  - Fewsmith, Joseph, 1941 (Folder 50)
  - Ficke, Hermann Styles, 192- 1943 (Folder 51)
  - Field, Carter, 1932 (Folder 52)
  - Field, Marshall, Jr., 1960 (Folder 53)
  - Fields, Don, 1965 (Folder 54)
  - Fields, Harold, 1929 (Folder 55)
  - Fifield, Margaret F., 1930 (Folder 56)
  - Finch, Edward R., 1932 (Folder 57)
  - Finch, Eleanor K., 1939 (Folder 58)
  - Finch, Robert H., 1962-1965 (Folder 59)
  - Findlater, J. G., 1934 (Folder 60)
  - Findley, Paul, 1961 (Folder 61)
  - Finger, Ray, 1923 (Folder 62)
  - Finley, John, 1933 (Folder 63)
  - Finley, John H., 1924 (Folder 64)
  - Finn, Jay, 1932 (Folder 65)
  - Finn, Joseph H., 1943 (Folder 66)
  - Fish, Hamilton, Jr., 1936 (Folder 67)
  - Fishbein, Morris, 1933-1948 (Folder 68)
  - Fisher, Atwood M., 1932 (Folder 69)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1932-1937 (Folder 70)
  - Fitch, Mary Marden, 1933 (Folder 71)
  - Fite, E. D., 1928 (Folder 72)
  - Fitzgerald, Harold, 1955 (Folder 73)
  - Fitzgerald, John, 1933-1953 (Folder 74)
  - Fitzgerald, W. S., 1921 (Folder 75)
  - Fitzpatrick, Daniel R., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fitzpatrick, F. Stuart, 1924-1939 (Folder 2)
  - Flaig, Charles M., 1937 (Folder 3)
  - Fleeson, Doris, 1931 (Folder 4)
  - Fleisher, Max, 1934 (Folder 5)
  - Fleming, Arthur S., 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Flesher, Bernard R., 1934 (Folder 7)
  - Fletcher, Clifford J., 1954 (Folder 8)
  - Fletcher, C. Scott, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Fletcher, Henry D., 1936 (Folder 10)
  - Flexner, Abraham, 1930 (Folder 11)
  - Flexner, Bernard, 1933-1942 (Folder 12)
  - Flood, Earl D., 1963 (Folder 13)
  - Florsheim, Milton S., 1932 (Folder 14)
  - Flory, Walter L., 1920-1950 (Folder 15)
  - Flynn, Edward J., 1933-1947 (Folder 16)
  - Flynn, John T., 1938-1958 (Folder 17)
  - Flynn, William, 1958 (Folder 18)
  - Fogle, W. H., 1937 (Folder 19)
  - Foley, James A., 1932 (Folder 20)
  - Folsom, Marion B., 1936-1965 (Folder 21)
  - Ford, Anne, 1939 (Folder 22)
  - Ford, George B., 1929-1933 (Folder 23)
  - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., 1960 (Folder 24)
  - Ford, John C., 1949 (Folder 25)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1942 (Folder 26)
  - Forker, Eugene, 1936 (Folder 27)
  - Forman, Philip, 1929-1931 (Folder 28)
  - Forney, Charles, 1934 (Folder 29)
  - Forrestal, James, 1945-1966 (Folder 30)
  - Fortier, M. L., 1927-1929 (Folder 31)
  - Foster, Lew, 1933 (Folder 32)
  - Foulk, Thomas B., 1935-1936 (Folder 33)
  - Fouts, Elwood, 1951 (Folder 34)
  - Fovhy, W. A., 1928-1933 (Folder 35)
  - Fowkes, Margaret H., 1942 (Folder 36)
  - Fowler, Gene, 1947-1951 (Folder 37)
  - Fowler, Harold N., 1933 (Folder 38)
  - Fox, Charles E., 1927-1933 (Folder 39)
  - Fox, Dixon Ryan, 1933-1934 (Folder 40)
  - Fox, Edward B., 1932-1936 (Folder 41)
  - Fox, Edward Whiting, 1943 (Folder 42)
  - Fox, Harry J., 1949 (Folder 43)
  - Frackenthal, Frank D., 1923 (Folder 44)
  - Francis, Arthur Y., 1927 (Folder 45)
  - Francis, Clarence, 1936 (Folder 46)
  - Francis, Warren, 1954 (Folder 47)
  - Frank, Alda, 1933 (Folder 48)
  - Frank, Gerold, 1932 (Folder 49)
  - Frank, Glenn, 1932 (Folder 50)
  - Frank, Jerome N., 1934-1940 (Folder 51)
  - Frank, Norman, 1966 (Folder 52)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1921-1955 (Folder 53)
  - Frankham, Charles R., 1927 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Franklin, John M., 1936 (Folder 2)
  - Fraser, L., 1917 (Folder 3)
  - Fraser, M. G., 1928 (Folder 4)
  - Frater, Edward L., 1934 (Folder 5)
  - Freed, Allie S., 1934-1937 (Folder 6)
  - Freed, David A., 1965 (Folder 7)
  - Freeland, Archie T., 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Freeman, Donald, 1932 (Folder 9)
  - Freeman, Roger A., 1960-1965 (Folder 10)
  - Frederick, J. M. H., 1933 (Folder 11)
  - Freidel, Frank, 1954-1966 (Folder 12)
  - Frelinghuysen, Peter, Jr., 1957 (Folder 13)
  - French, Allison T., 1922 (Folder 14)
  - French, Fred F., 1932-1936 (Folder 15)
  - French, Oakleigh R., 1954 (Folder 16)
  - French, Patterson, n.d. (Folder 17)
  - Friant, Julien N., 1932 (Folder 18)
  - Fricke, Charles, 1927 (Folder 19)
  - Friebolin, Carl D., 1919-1961 (Folder 20)
  - Fried, Rainer, 1964 (Folder 21)
  - Friedland, M. N., 1932 (Folder 22)
  - Friese, Richard P., 1966 (Folder 23)
  - Friesner, A. Herman, 1948 (Folder 24)
  - Frooks, S. Leighton, 1931 (Folder 25)
  - Frost, Frederic G., 1934 (Folder 26)
  - Fruehauf, Harvey C., 1932 (Folder 27)
  - Fry, Elizabeth D., 1919-1932 (Folder 28)
  - Fryer, William T., 1933 (Folder 29)
  - Fuchs, Elfriya, 1934 (Folder 30)
  - Fuchs, R. F., 1928 (Folder 31)
  - Fuerth, Edna, 1936 (Folder 32)
  - Fulbright, Freeman, 1963 (Folder 33)
  - Fulbright, J. W., 1948 (Folder 34)
  - Fuller, Hugh N., 1926-1933 (Folder 35)
  - Fulton, B. F., 1933 (Folder 36)
  - Fulton, George P., 1933 (Folder 37)
  - Furlong, William H., 1936 (Folder 38)
  - Furniss, E. S., 1928-1929 (Folder 39)
  - Furr, Sherman S., 1932 (Folder 40)
  - Fusfeld, Daniel R., 1954 (Folder 41)
  - Gage, Daniel S., 1947 (Folder 42)
  - Gage, Jack R., 1961 (Folder 43)
  - Gans, Raymond B., 1954 (Folder 44)
  - Gale, James H., 1963 (Folder 45)
  - Gale, Zona, 1934 (Folder 46)
  - Gall, John C., 1943 (Folder 47)
  - Gallup, George, 1949 (Folder 48)
  - Galvin, G. E., 1960-1964 (Folder 49)
  - Gamble, Harry P., 1936 (Folder 50)
  - Gambrell, E. Smythe, 1965 (Folder 51)
  - Gancy, B. M., 1934 (Folder 52)
  - Gannon, Leo, 1935 (Folder 53)
  - Gant, V. F., 1934 (Folder 54)
  - Gardner, John, 1933 (Folder 55)
  - Gardner, O. Max, 1942-1966 (Folder 56)
  - Garey, Eugene L., 1939 (Folder 57)
  - Garfield, James R., 1920 (Folder 58)
  - Garis, Roger, 1943 (Folder 59)
  - Garland, D. F., 1922 (Folder 60)
  - Garling, Patrick E., 1953 (Folder 61)
  - Garner, G. H., 1935-1947 (Folder 62)
  - Garner, G. W., 1916-1926 (Folder 63)
  - Garrett, L. D., 1932-1934 (Folder 64)
  - Garrett, Paul W., 1937-1942 (Folder 65)
  - Garrison, Curits W., 1943 (Folder 66)
  - Garvan, Francis P., 1932 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Garvey, Dan E., 1949 (Folder 2)
  - Gary, Herbert S., 1965 (Folder 3)
  - Gaston, Herbert E., 1932 (Folder 4)
  - Gates, Charles A., 1931 (Folder 5)
  - Gates, Ralph F., 1945-1946 (Folder 6)
  - Gates, Thomas S., 1964 (Folder 7)
  - Gaudet, Frederick G., 1933 (Folder 8)
  - Gault, Robert H., 1929-1931 (Folder 9)
  - Gaus, John M., 1930 (Folder 10)
  - Gavit, J. P., 1918 (Folder 11)
  - Gay, Frederick N., 1939 (Folder 12)
  - Geary, John E., 1934 (Folder 13)
  - Gebhart, John C., 1936 (Folder 14)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel, 1936 (Folder 15)
  - Gee, Wilson, 1929 (Folder 16)
  - Gehlke, Charles E., 1919-1939 (Folder 17)
  - Geiger, G. L., 1952 (Folder 18)
  - Geiser, Karl F., 1918-1940 (Folder 19)
  - Geismar, Siegfried, 1932-1958 (Folder 20)
  - Geist, William, 1934 (Folder 21)
  - Geive, Karl Y., 1919 (Folder 22)
  - Genaver, Emily, 1947-1948 (Folder 23)
  - Genney, John J., 1951 (Folder 24)
  - Gentry, Brady, 1955 (Folder 25)
  - Gentsch, Frank F., 1936 (Folder 26)
  - Genung, George L., 1933 (Folder 27)
  - Gerard, James W., 1938 (Folder 28)
  - Gerould, Russell, 1943 (Folder 29)
  - Gesell, G. A., 1923 (Folder 30)
  - Getts, Clark H., 1948-1951 (Folder 31)
  - Gibbons, J. M., 1931-1933 (Folder 32)
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1943 (Folder 33)
  - Gibson, J. C., 1957-1958 (Folder 34)
  - Gibson, Tom L., 1951 (Folder 35)
  - Gifford, James P., 1942 (Folder 36)
  - Gilbert, Parker, 1937 (Folder 37)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia C., 1924-1933 (Folder 38)
  - Giles, John Warren, 1943 (Folder 39)
  - Gill, R. O., 1934 (Folder 40)
  - Gillespie, S. Hazard, 1956 (Folder 41)
  - Gillette, Guy M., 1942 (Folder 42)
  - Gillin, John L., 1927-1928 (Folder 43)
  - Gilson, Mary B., 1934 (Folder 44)
  - Gimma, Joseph, 1961 (Folder 45)
  - Ginn, Lowen E., 1939 (Folder 46)
  - Giorgi, Andrew V., 1952 (Folder 47)
  - Gipson, J. H., 1952-1953 (Folder 48)
  - Gipson, Lawrence H., 1927 (Folder 49)
  - Girsh, Myer L., 1929 (Folder 50)
  - Giuliani, Peter, 1960 (Folder 51)
  - Glass, Carter, 1939-1961 (Folder 52)
  - Glass, James M., 1953 (Folder 53)
  - Glassman, Leo M., 1933 (Folder 54)
  - Glendon, George A., 1931-1939 (Folder 55)
  - Glens Falls Indemnity Co., 1952 (Folder 56)
  - Glotzbach, George Z., 1963 (Folder 57)
  - Glueck, Eleanor T., 1946 (Folder 58)
  - Glueck, Shelton, 1930-1962 (Folder 59)
  - Godshall, Leon W., 1928 (Folder 60)
  - Goebel, G., 1933 (Folder 61)
  - Goff, F. H., 1920-1922 (Folder 62)
  - Goldberg, W. A., 1930 (Folder 63)
  - Goldman, Eric F., 1952-1963 (Folder 64)
  - Goldman, Mayer C., 1932 (Folder 65)
  - Goldstein, Jonah J., 1933 (Folder 66)
  - Goldstein, Ruth, 1932 (Folder 67)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1949-1965 (Folder 68)
  - Goldwater, Monroe, 1936-1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Golin, May M., 1945 (Folder 2)
  - Gonier, Leonard E., 1961 (Folder 3)
  - Goode, J. D., 1934 (Folder 4)
  - Goodier, James H., 1938-1939 (Folder 5)
  - Goodman, Carl C., 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Goodman, Joseph D., 1932 (Folder 7)
  - Goodman, J. Harvey, 1932 (Folder 8)
  - Goodman, S., n.d. (Folder 9)
  - Goodman, William, 1955 (Folder 10)
  - Goodrich, Herbert F., 1930 (Folder 11)
  - Goodwillie, C. G., 1935-1936 (Folder 12)
  - Goodwin, Carl D., 1934 (Folder 13)
  - Goodwin, D. R., 1930 (Folder 14)
  - Gordon, Arthur G., 1932 (Folder 15)
  - Gordon, Max, 1936-1937 (Folder 16)
  - Gordon, William, 1914-1931 (Folder 17)
  - Gosnell, Cullen B., 1934 (Folder 18)
  - Gott, Philip P., 1933 (Folder 19)
  - Gould, Symon, 1933 (Folder 20)
  - Gourich, Paul P., 1932 (Folder 21)
  - Graffis, Herb, 1933-1934 (Folder 22)
  - Graham, Frank P., 1934-1936 (Folder 23)
  - Graham, George A., 1934 (Folder 24)
  - Graham, Lloyd S., 1934 (Folder 25)
  - Graham, Otis L., 1966 (Folder 26)
  - Graham, Philip L., 1964 (Folder 27)
  - Granducci, O. S., 1936 (Folder 28)
  - Grant, A. W., 1948-1956 (Folder 29)
  - Grant, E. S., 1934 (Folder 30)
  - Graham, N. M., 1912 (Folder 31)
  - Grant, J. A. C., 1931-1941 (Folder 32)
  - Grant, John L., 1929 (Folder 33)
  - Grant, Madison, 1934 (Folder 34)
  - Grant, W. T., 1937 (Folder 35)
  - Gratz, Earl Jay, 1927 (Folder 36)
  - Graubard, S. J., 1954 (Folder 37)
  - Graul, Jacob, 1926 (Folder 38)
  - Graves, John T., 1942 (Folder 39)
  - Graves, Richard, 1932 (Folder 40)
  - Graves, W. Brooke, 1927 (Folder 41)
  - Gray, Carl R., 1936 (Folder 42)
  - Gray, G. D., 1927 (Folder 43)
  - Gray, Joseph M. M., 1935 (Folder 44)
  - Gray, W. S., 1961 (Folder 45)
  - Grayson, Cary, 1932-1936 (Folder 46)
  - Green, Abel, 1946 (Folder 47)
  - Green, Dwight N., 1948 (Folder 48)
  - Green, George, 1921-1961 (Folder 49)
  - Green, Henry, 1938 (Folder 50)
  - Green, J. G., 1965 (Folder 51)
  - Green, John W., 1955 (Folder 52)
  - Green, Leon, 1941 (Folder 53)
  - Green, William, 1927-1934 (Folder 54)
  - Greenbaum, Edward S., 1938 (Folder 55)
  - Greenbaum, L. S., 1932 (Folder 56)
  - Greenblatt, Helen, 1934 (Folder 57)
  - Greene, E. B., 1919 (Folder 58)
  - Greene, Henry Copley, 1936 (Folder 59)
  - Greene, Marc T., 1965 (Folder 60)
  - Greenhaugh, H. W., 1951 (Folder 61)
  - Greenslet, Ferris, 1932-1933 (Folder 62)
  - Greenspan, Morris, n.d. (Folder 63)
  - Greet, W. Cabell, 1937-1953 (Folder 64)
  - Grenier, John, 1963-1964 (Folder 65-66)
  - Griffin, Gerald T., 1961 (Folder 67)
  - Griffin, H., 1932-1933 (Folder 68)
  - Griffin, Robert P., 1966 (Folder 69)
  - Griffin, William, 1934 (Folder 70)
  - Griffith, C., 1952 (Folder 71)
  - Griffith, E. G. 1936 (Folder 72)
  - Griffith, M. Louise, 1928 (Folder 73)
  - Grimm, J. Hugo, 1932 (Folder 74)
  - Grimes, George, 1942 (Folder 75)
  - Grimson, Godmunder, 1934 (Folder 76)
  - Gristede, Margaret G., 1933 (Folder 77)
  - Griswold, Denny, 1942 (Folder 78)
  - Griswold, Glenn, 1934-1942 (Folder 79)
  - Gros, Robert R., 1939-1965 (Folder 80)
  - Grossman, Mary B., 1921-1923 (Folder 81)
  - Grover, D. C., 1933 (Folder 82)
  - Gruenberg, B. C., 1931 (Folder 83)
  - Gruenberg, Frederick P., 1933 (Folder 84)
  - Gruening, Ernest N., 1934-1936 (Folder 85)
  - Gruenther, Homer H., 1939 (Folder 86)
  - Guest, Leon C., 1932 (Folder 87)
  - Guggenheim, Harry F., 1937-1942 (Folder 88)
  - Guinzburg, Harold K., 1949 (Folder 89)
  - Guitteau, William B., 1946-1962 (Folder 90)
  - Gulick, Luther, 1926-1936 (Folder 91)
  - Guptill, E. Loise, 1934 (Folder 92)
  - Gustafson, G. J., 1961-1966 (Folder 93)
  - Guthrie, Cannop, 1941 (Folder 94)
  - Guyton, Mary L., 1932-1933 (Folder 95)
  - Gwinn, Ralph, 1957 (Folder 96)
  - Hachmeister, Louise, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hacker, Louis M., 1931-1959 (Folder 2)
  - Hackett, Byrne, 1936 (Folder 3)
  - Hackett, Francis, 1936 (Folder 4)
  - Hackman, Turner K., 1934 (Folder 5)
  - Hadden, Briton, 1927 (Folder 6)
  - Hadley, A. B., 1929 (Folder 7)
  - Hadley, Herbert, 1927 (Folder 8)
  - Hafer, Eveanor, 1930 (Folder 9)
  - Hagedorn, Hermann, 1952 (Folder 10)
  - Hageman, Miller, 1933 (Folder 11)
  - Hagemann, H. Frederick, Jr., 1954 (Folder 12)
  - Hahn, H. C., 1934 (Folder 13)
  - Haight, Raymond, 1944 (Folder 14)
  - Haile, Elster M., 1943-1950 (Folder 15)
  - Haimes, Therese, 1934 (Folder 16)
  - Haines, Charles Grove, 1926-1936 (Folder 17)
  - Hale, William G., 1931 (Folder 18)
  - Hall, Albert H., 1931 (Folder 19)
  - Hall, Arnold Bennett, 1926-1932 (Folder 20)
  - Hall, Fred S., 1930-1931 (Folder 21)
  - Hall, Jerome, 1936 (Folder 22)
  - Hall, Katharine, 1933-1936 (Folder 23)
  - Hall, Kent B., 1943 (Folder 24)
  - Hall, Leonard W., 1954-1965 (Folder 25)
  - Hall, M. F., 1931 (Folder 26)
  - Hall, Reuben T., 1936 (Folder 27)
  - Hall, Samuel S., 1926 (Folder 28)
  - Hall, William, 1934 (Folder 29)
  - Hallberg, Charles W., 1955 (Folder 30)
  - Halle, Catherine, 1934 (Folder 31)
  - Hallenbeck, C. A., 1927 (Folder 32)
  - Haller, William, 1933 (Folder 33)
  - Halpern, Irving W., 1931 (Folder 34)
  - Halstead, M. R., 1934 (Folder 35)
  - Halstead, James A., 1966 (Folder 36)
  - Haman, Albert L., III, 1963 (Folder 37)
  - Hamilton, C. G., 1934 (Folder 38)
  - Hamilton, John, 1939 (Folder 39)
  - Hamilton, O. J., 1932 (Folder 40)
  - Hamilton, R. R., 1932 (Folder 41)
  - Hamlin, Helen T., 1927 (Folder 42)
  - Hammer, Ernest E. L., 1934-1935 (Folder 43)
  - Hammond, J. D., 1957 (Folder 44)
  - Hammond, M. B., 1918 (Folder 45)
  - Hammond, William, 1951 (Folder 46)
  - Hand, Charles, 1947 (Folder 47)
  - Handler, Milton, 1931-1938 (Folder 48)
  - Hanford, A. C., 1927 (Folder 49)
  - Hanighen, Frank C., 1955-1963 (Folder 50)
  - Hankin, Gregory, 1933 (Folder 51)
  - Hanna, Francis D., 1929 (Folder 52)
  - Hanna, John, 1932-1954 (Folder 53)
  - Hanna, Paul, 1938 (Folder 54)
  - Hanna, Philip S., 1938-1941 (Folder 55)
  - Hanrahan, John, 1934 (Folder 56)
  - Hansen, Allen O., 1928 (Folder 57)
  - Hansen, Harry, 1939 (Folder 58)
  - Hansen, Henry A., 1952 (Folder 59)
  - Hansen, Julia Butler, 1963 (Folder 60)
  - Hapgood, Norman, 1932-1936 (Folder 61)
  - Happ, Leonard C., 1962 (Folder 62)
  - Hard, William, 1934-1937 (Folder 63)
  - Harder, George W., 1931 (Folder 64)
  - Harding, H. F., 1954-1955 (Folder 65)
  - Hardison, Robert, 1932 (Folder 66)
  - Hardy, Porter, Jr., 1958 (Folder 67)
  - Hargest, William M., 1931 (Folder 68)
  - Hargitt, W. P., 1933-1934 (Folder 69)
  - Harley, Herbert, 1916-1929 (Folder 70)
  - Harlow, Bryce N., 1962 (Folder 71)
  - Harmon, H. G., 1951 (Folder 72)
  - Harnett, Charles A., 1934 (Folder 73)
  - Harno, Albert J., 1927-1939 (Folder 74)
  - Harrell, Charles, 1949 (Folder 75)
  - Harriman, Henry I., 1934 (Folder 76)
  - Harriman, Mary A., 1939 (Folder 77)
  - Harriman, W. Averell, 1934-1939 (Folder 78)
  - Harrington, Virginia, 1931 (Folder 79)
  - Harris, Bessie Holley, 1954 (Folder 80)
  - Harris, E. L., 1934 (Folder 81)
  - Harris, George B., 1924-1943 (Folder 82)
  - Harris, John F., 1953 (Folder 83)